SHANTANU PATEL

SAP ABAP on HANA Consultant.

SUMMARY

I am dedicated and hard-working SAP consultant with over 4 years of experience in SAP ABAP on HANA. Actively looking for an opportunity that utilizes my honed skills and helps me grow professionally. I am a team player and proactive learner who is willing to walk the extra mile to ensure the success of my organization.

EXPERIENCE

Technical Consultant

05/2023 - Present

PwC Benin

- Client Description: West African Textile based Greenfield implementation project.
 PROPERTY OF THE PRO
- Worked as ABAP technical consultant for PP/QM, MM/EWM, FI/CO and SD module .
- Developed Adobe forms for various FI/CO, SD and PP objects.
- Worked on BADIs, Customer Exit and User Exits.
- Worked as a lead developer for MM based Inbound Gate Entry Application.
- Worked as a trainer in 'Basics of ABAP' training program conducted within a project to new joiners.
- · Created multiple interactive reports.
- Worked on FI substitutions and validations.
- Basics knowledge of OData.
- Proficient in the design and development of complex application using Module Pool.
- Developed ABAP reports utilizing ABAP OOPS concepts.
- Worked with FI/CO team for Pre order costing application development .
- Worked on Eclipse on Top of ADT where I created CDS views and utilised the same in ABAP reports.
- Basic Knowledge of AMDP Functions and Procedure.

Application Development Analyst

12/2022 - 04/2023

Accenture Melbourne

Client Description: BHP Billiton is an Australian multinational mining, metals and natural gas

- petroleum company headquartered in Melbourne, Victoria, Australia.

 Worked as ABAP technical consultant in HCM dev team.
- Handled all RICEF objects using Object oriented approach for all the developments.
- Handled Service now Tickets, providing technical analysis, support bug fixes within SLA.
- Created reusable technical documents with quality.
- Worked on file interfaces to send the data into AL11 file directories.
- Worked in Performance optimization SCI, ATC, traces.

Application Development Associate

05/2021 - 12/2022

Accenture

Client: AESG PATH 2.0.

- Worked as an Application development analyst in S4 Greenfield Implementation project.
- Delivered RICEFW objects with minimum defects.
- Delivered proxy interfaces within deadline across module such as MM, PPM, Banking, etc.
- Analyzed many complex standard and custom programs to provide solution to many configuration issues.
- · Worked on FI substitutions and validations.

Application Development Associate

11/2020 - 05/2021

Accenture Anz

Client: AESG ANZ BAU.

- Worked as an associate developer fulfilling client requirements.
- Worked across FICO, MM modules.
- Involved in Enhancement works as well as new custom Reports.
- Worked in modification and development of adobe forms.
- · Delivered Objects with almost zero defects within deadline.
- Created reusable technical documents with quality.



KEY ACHIEVEMENTS

- ABAP with SAP Netweaver7.50 Certified
- ABAP for SAP HANA2.0Certified

SKILLS

SAP ABAP · Module Pool · OOPs ABAP ·

Adobe forms · DDIC · BADI · CDS ·

Eclipse · AMDP

LANGUAGES

English Proficient ••••

Hindi Proficient ••••

EDUCATION

Bachelors of Engineering (B.E)

Shri Ramdebaba College of Engineering and Management 08/2017 - 07/2020